Guide to the Lorraine García-Nakata papers M2056
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- LGN exhibition & event posters
  - Exhibition & event publicity with LGN (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Handbills and pamphlets with LGN as artist, curator, or museum affiliate (especially Galeria de la Raza).
- Exhibition & event publicity (other artists)
  Many are posters for art exhibitions, but there is also publicity for films, music, and political and cultural events. The majority of events are in San Francisco. Some are special silkscreen versions of mass-produced posters.
  - Exhibition & event publicity posters & fliers (Box 37, Folder 7)
    Mostly Mexican Museum.
  - Event & exhibition posters (Box 40, Folder 1, Box 41, Folders 1-3, Map-folder 42, Map-folder 43)
- Art by other artists
  - prints and original art (Box 40, Folder 2-3, Box 41, Folders 6-7, Map-folder 45)
  - Disney-themed art by convict on San Quentin death row (Box 40, Folder 4)
    According to an accompnying note, these were given to LGN while she was a local artist in the San Quentin Arts Program, 1988-1990.
  - Posters - art & politics (Box 41, Folders 4-5)